A Guide to the Records of the Fairhope Industrial Association and the Fairhope Single Tax Corporation, 1893-1997
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Records of the Fairhope Industrial Association and the Fairhope Single Tax Corporation 1893-1997
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10517-a, -b
This collection consists of 34,800 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was made a gift to the Library by the Fairhope Single Tax Corporation, 340 Fairhope Avenue, Fairhope, Alabama on March 26, 2001.
Scope and Content Information
The Records of the Fairhope Industrial Association and the Fairhope Single Tax Corporation, 1893-1997, consist of ca. 34,800 items, chiefly concerning the routine activities of the Corporation. Records include correspondence and papers, legal files, financial records, annual reports, minutes of the Board, printed articles, maps, and issues of the Fairhope Courier. Included are the correspondence and papers of Secretaries of the Corporation, Ernest B. Gaston, Cornelius "Cornie" Alonzo Gaston, and Gale W. Rowe, concerning routine and special activities of the Corporation; annual reports, 1944-1977; business papers and bound volumes, 1895-1993; and, legal documents and other papers concerning the Rezner v. Fairhope Suit. There are also early papers and correspondence of James Bellangee, his daughter, Anne B. Call, Ernest B. Gaston, Joseph Fels, the Fairhope Cemetery, the Fairhope Courier, and Lydia J. Newcomb Comings.
In Rezner vs. Fairhope Single Tax Corporation, Rudolph John Rezner and other resident citizens and non-member lessees of Fairhope Single Tax Corporation filed complaint against the corporation for not lawfully upholding its constitution as a non-profit organization based on the principles of Henry George. The case challenged the constitution's statement of equitable approximation, commenting that the constitution fails to provide that a member must be a lessee; that the Fairhope Single Tax Corporation pays real property and personal property taxes for its lessees even though rent determination remains the same; that there has been a substantially greater percentage of increase on rents on country leaseholds compared to the rents on city leaseholds, thereby creating an atmosphere of discrimination against country lessees; and, that the violation of constitutional requirements has diminished the status of non-member lessees and created a situation in which the non-member lessees' properties have become essentially unmarketable. Plaintiffs also challenged the right of the Fairhope Single Tax Corporation's attempt to reorganize as a "For Profit" corporation without notice to its lessees.
Historical information may be found in the papers and volumes of this collection, such as "History of Fairhope..." in Gale W. Rowe's papers, as well as in Paul M. Gaston's book, Man and Mission: E. B. Gaston and the Origins of the Fairhope Single Tax Colony, The Black Belt Press: Montgomery, Alabama, 1993.
Contents List
- Correspondence and Papers of Fairhope and Related
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Letterbook of Ernest B. Gaston (1) 1895 (Folder 1-22)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, including correspondence with Joseph Fels (2) 1897-1906 (Folder 1-22)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Correspondence of James Bellangee, including correspondence with Joseph Fels (3) 1902-1911 (Folder 1-22)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Correspondence of James Bellangee re Amendment to Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Original Constitution (4) 1905-1913 (Folder 1-22)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Writings of James Bellangee (5) ca. 1900-1911 (Folder 1-22)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Printed re James Bellangee (6) 1894-1913 (Folder 1-22)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Correspondence of Anne B. Call (6 folders) (7-12) 1903-1936 (Folder 1-22)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Correspondence of Anne B. Call re death of father, James Bellangee (13) 1915 (Folder 1-22)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Scrapbook of Anne B. Call, including correspondence (2 folders) (14-15) 1930-1931 (Folder 1-22)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Scrapbook of Anne B. Call, including correspondence (3 folders) (16-18) 1932-1937 (Folder 1-22)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Minutes of the Fairhope Industrial Association, Vol. I & II (19-20) 1894-1896 (Folder 1-22)
  - Minutes of the Des Moines Single Tax Club (21) 1893-1894 (Folder 1-22)
  - Minutes of the Baldwin County Agricultural Society (22) 1897-1902 (Folder 1-22)
  - Fairhope Cemetery Correspondence (3 folders) (23-25) 1926-1965 (Folder 23-49)
  - Fairhope Cemetery Leases (2 folders) (26-27) 1937-1963 (Folder 23-49)
  - Fairhope Cemetery Meeting Minutes: A-B (28) 1926-1956 (Folder 23-49)
  - Fairhope Courier Correspondence: C (29) 1926 (Folder 23-49)
  - Fairhope Courier Correspondence: D-L (30) 1926 (Folder 23-49)
  - Fairhope Courier Correspondence: M-O (31) 1926 (Folder 23-49)
  - Fairhope Courier Correspondence: P-W (32) 1926 (Folder 23-49)
  - Fairhope Courier Correspondence: A-B (33) 1927-1929 (Folder 23-49)
  - Fairhope Courier Correspondence: C-D (34) 1927-1929 (Folder 23-49)
  - Fairhope Courier Correspondence: E-J (35) 1927-1929 (Folder 23-49)
  - Fairhope Courier Correspondence: K-L (36) 1927-1929 (Folder 23-49)
  - Fairhope Courier Correspondence: M-O (37) 1927-1929 (Folder 23-49)
  - Fairhope Courier Correspondence: P-R (38) 1927-1929 (Folder 23-49)
  - Fairhope Courier Correspondence: S (39) 1927-1929 (Folder 23-49)
  - Fairhope Courier Correspondence: T-V (40) 1927-1929 (Folder 23-49)
  - Fairhope Courier Correspondence: W-Z (41) 1927-1929 (Folder 23-49)
  - Lydia J. Newcomb Comings: Bank Statements (42) 1925 (Folder 23-49)
  - Lydia J. Newcomb Comings: Bank Statements (43) 1926 (Folder 23-49)
  - Lydia J. Newcomb Comings: Bank Statements (44) 1927 (Folder 23-49)
  - Lydia J. Newcomb Comings: Bank Statements (45) 1928 (Folder 23-49)
  - Lydia J. Newcomb Comings: Bank Statements (46) 1929 (Folder 23-49)
  - Lydia J. Newcomb Comings: Correspondence (47) 1912-1928 (Folder 23-49)
  - Lydia J. Newcomb Comings: Women's Clubs Yearbooks (48) 1903-1928 (Folder 23-49)
- Correspondence and Papers of Secretaries of Fairhope
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston: A (50) 1924-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston: B (51) 1929-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston: C (52) 1930-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston: D (53) 1931-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston: E-G (54) 1928-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston: Fairhope, Town of (55) 1930-1936 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston: H-K (56) 1930-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston: L-M (57) 1914-1934 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston: N-Q (58) 1931-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston: R-S (59) 1930-1936 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston: Rent Memorandums (60) 1931-1936 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston: T (61) 1915(1930-1936) (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston: W (62) 1930-1934 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston: Y (63) 1930-1934 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: A (64) 1931-1936 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: B-Bl (65) 1930-1936 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: Bo-Bu (66) 1930-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: C-Col (67) 1930-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: Com-Cu (68) 1929-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: D (69) 1930-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: E-F (70) 1930-1936 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: G (71) 1929-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: H (72) 1924-1936 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: I-J (73) 1930-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: K-L (74) 1930-1936 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: Ma (75) 1930-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: Mc (76) 1930-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: Me-Mu (77) 1930-1936 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: N-P (78) 1930-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: Q-R (79) 1929-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: S (80) 1930-1936 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: T-V (81) 1930-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: Wa (82) 1930-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Ernest B. Gaston, Inquiries: We-Wi (83) 1930-1935 (Folder 50-83)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: A (84) 1936-1955 (Folder 84-100)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Ba-Bi (85) 1934-1955 (Folder 84-100)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Bl-By (86) 1935-1951 (Folder 84-100)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Ca-Cl (87) 1933-1953 (Folder 84-100)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Co-Cu (88) 1936-1950 (Folder 84-100)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Da-Di (89) 1936-1953 (Folder 84-100)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Do-Dy (90) 1932-1952 (Folder 84-100)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: E (91) 1936-1954 (Folder 84-100)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: F (92) 1932-1955 (Folder 84-100)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Fairhope, Town of (3 folders) (93-95) 1934-1956 (Folder 84-100)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Letters of Inquiry (96) 1936-1940 (Folder 84-100)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Letters of Inquiry (97) 1937-1946 (Folder 84-100)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Ga-Graham (98) 1935-1953 (Folder 84-100)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Grant-Gu (99) 1937-1953 (Folder 84-100)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Ha-Hc (100) 1936-1955 (Folder 84-100)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Hi-Hu (101) 1936-1958 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: I-K (102) 1927-1953 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: L (103) 1936-1951 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Ma-Mc (104) 1932-1954 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Me-Mu (105) 1937-1954 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: N-O (106) 1935-1951 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: P-Q (107) 1931-1954 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: R (108) 1935-1953 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: S-Sl (109) 1934-1954 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Scrapbook (3 folders) (110-112) 1934-1935 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Sm-Sp (113) 1929-1952 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: St-Sw (114) 1936-1954 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: T (115) 1935-1953 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: U-V (116) 1937-1953 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: W (117) 1935-1952 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Y-Z (118) 1936-1952 (Folder 101-118)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: A (119) 1935-1961 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Ba (120) 1935-1954 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Be-Bl (121) 1935-1954 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Br-By (122) 1933-1955 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: C (123) 1935-1960 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: D-E (124) 1934-1954 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Day Books (2 folders) (125-126) 1937-1940 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Delinquent Rents (2 folders) (127-128) 1935-1941 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: F (129) 1935-1954 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: G (130) 1935-1954 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Ha (131) 1935-1954 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: He-Hu (132) 1935-1954 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Home Owners' Loan Corporation (133) 1933-1947 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: I-J (134) 1935-1955 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: K (135) 1936-1953 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: L (136) 1937-1953 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Ma-Mc (137) 1932-1954 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Me-My (138) 1931-1949 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: N-O (139) 1928-1952 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Notices of Application for Land (140) 1939 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: P-Q (141) 1935-1954 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Ra-Ri (142) 1936-1948 (Folder 119-142)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Ro-Ry (143) 1932-1951 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Sa-Sl (144) 1921-1955 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Sm-Sw (145) 1929-1951 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: T-V (146) 1938-1951 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: A.M. and Elva Troyer (147) 1938 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: W-We (148) 1933-1954 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Wh-Wr (149) 1933-1953 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Z (150) 1939-1950 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: A-B (151) 1955-1970 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Baldwin County Savings and Loan (152) 1951-1958 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: C-D (153) 1955-1971 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: E-G (154) 1955-1971 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Bruce Evans, Jr. Files (4 folders) (155-158) 1955-1968 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Bruce Evans, Jr. Files ' Salaries (159) 1961 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Bruce Evans, Jr. Files ' Tax Collector, M.H. Wilkins (160) 1934-1951 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Bruce Evans, Jr. Files ' Tax Collector, M.H. Wilkins (161) 1952-1955 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Bruce Evans, Jr. Files ' Tax Collector, M.H. Wilkins (162) 1956-1965 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Fairhope, City of (2 folders) (163-164) 1955-1971 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Federal Housing and Veterans Administration -165 1939 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Financial Statements (166) 1953-1969 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Foreign Country Correspondence (167) 1933-1967 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: H-K (168) 1954-1971 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Henry George Miscellaneous (169) 1953-1972 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Henry George School of Social Science (170) 1946 (Folder 143-170)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: L (171) 1955-1968 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: M (172) 1955-1969 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Marietta Johnson School of Organic Education (173) 1942-1963 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: N-R (174) 1951-1971 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: S (175) 1939-1971 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: Secretary's Reports (176) 1954-1970 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Cornelius A. Gaston: T-Z (177) 1954-1971 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: A (178) [Alabama, Appointments, Assessments, etc.] 1974-1993 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: B-H (179) 1966-1997 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Board of Review (2 folders) (180-181) 1975-1980 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Centennial Hall (182) 1993 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Centennial Celebration (5 folders) (183-187) 1991-1995 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Correspondence (188) 1979-1994 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Council Proceedings (3 folders) (189-191) 1975-1981 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Crittenden Enterprises (192) 1975-1981 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Daphne, Fairhope Area Directory (193) 1962 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Economics (194) 1977-1996 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Finance (195) 1986-1997 (Folder 171-195)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Paul M. Gaston (196) 1978-1993 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Donald W. Gooden (197) 1980-1985 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Henry George Foundation of America (198) 1972-1994 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Henry George Institute (199) 1971-1974 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Henry George School of Social Science (200) 1960-1991 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: History of Fairhope, including articles (201) 1986-1991 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Idlewild (202) 1996 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: I-L (203) 1973-1996 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Letters of Inquiry (204) 1960-1971 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Letters of Inquiry (205) 1972-1997 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: M-O (206) 1983-1993 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Membership Correspondence (207) 1975-1995 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Moyd Property (208) 1970-1981 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: P-R (209) 1978-1994 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Reimbursement for Expenses (210) 1977-1978 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Reimbursement for Expenses ' Sam Dyson (211) 1977-1979 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: S-Z (212) 1986-1996 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Special Referendum Ballot Results (213) 1979 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: State and City Elections (214) 1954-1966 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Gale W. Rowe: Taxation and Property Equalization (215) 1976-1996 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Pension Fund ' Government Forms (216) 1975 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Pension Fund ' Insurance (217) 1974-1977 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Pension Fund ' Internal Revenue Service and Department of Labor (2 folders) (218-219) 1972-1978 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Pension Fund ' Pension Plan (220) 1969-1971 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Pension Fund ' Termination (2 folders) (221) 1977-1978 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Pension Fund ' Trustees Reports (222-223) 1973-1974 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Pension Fund ' Trustees Reports (224) (Folders 225-251) 1975-1977 (Folder 196-224)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Questionnaires (225) 1975 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Questionnaires (226) 1975 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Questionnaires (227) 1976 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Questionnaires (228) 1976 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Questionnaire Analysis (229) 1976 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data (230) 1904-1982 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data (231) 1956-1981 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data (232) 1962-1985 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data (233) 1962-1985 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data (234) 1962-1985 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data (235) 1968-1979 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data (236) 1980-1996 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data (237) 1982 (Folder 225-251)